Finding Aid for Career Planning and Placement (University of Michigan) publications, 1977-1993
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Career Planning and Placement (University of Michigan) publications, 1977-1993 1977-1993
University of Michigan. Career Planning and Placement.
0.6 linear ft.
0549 Bimu B6 C271 2
Publications produced by the University of Michigan's office of Career Planning and Placement, includes miscellaneous annual reports, brochures, and newsletters. Also includes printed materials regarding the Public Service Intern Program and the Washington Summer Intern Program.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
These records were transferred from the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs (donor no. 5013 ), 1991.
The record group is open without restriction.
Publications of the Career Planning and Placement Office include annual reports, manuals, newsletters, brochures, material related to workshops, Job Bulletin, 1992-193, as well as printed materials regarding the Public Service Intern Program and the Washington Summer Intern Program.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Career Planning and Placement.; University of Michigan. Public Service Intern Program.; University of Michigan. Washington Summer Intern Program.
Genre Terms:
Annual reports.; Brochures.; Newsletters.
- Unit Publications
  - Brochures (Box 1)
    - General, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Programs and workshops, 1983-1992 (Box 1)
  - Bulletins
    - Job bulletin, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Flyers (Box 1)
  - Manuals
    - Career briefs, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
    - Career planning resource handbook,[1988] (Box 1)
    - Guide to counseling and student services, 1971/1972, 1974/1975 (Box 1)
    - Guide to experiential learning, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
    - LS&A faculty and staff handbook for the University of Michigan Business Intern Program, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Placement manual, 1971/1972, 1977/1978, 1979/1980, 1985/1986 (Box 1)
    - Pre-law, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Pre-med, 1979-1989 (Box 2)
    - Writing reference letters: a guide for faculty, teaching assistants and staff (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous and general (Box 2)
  - Newsletters
    - Interview, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
      (volume 2:no.1, 1978 September; v.2:no.4 1978 April; v.2:no.8, 1978 December-v.2:no.12, 1979 April )
    - Minority network (Box 2)
    - Pre-med newsletter (Box 2)
  - Programs
    - Career days, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Public Service Intern Program
    - Alumni directory, [1984] (Box 2)
    - Annual reports, 1976-1979 (Box 2)
    - Program handbook, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Reports
    - Annual report, 1974/75-1992/93 (Box 2)
    - Factors in employer evaluation of higher education applicants, 1980 (Box 2)
    - Follow-up report, 1992-1993, 2 volumes (Box 2)
    - Monthly report, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
    - Strategic plan, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Washington Summer Intern Program
    - Annual reports, 1971-1974 (Box 2)